{"sid": "6V1GP0MTEDYB_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 338427, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 338428, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 345789]], "time_left_end": "293", "answered_time": 345789, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "293", "question_time_start": 345790, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["calc_7", 350012], ["calc_+", 350971], ["calc_8", 351883], ["calc_+", 352654], ["calc_9", 353431], ["calc_8", 354087], ["calc_=", 354783], ["submit", 359831]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "279", "answered_time": 359831, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "279", "question_time_start": 359832, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["submit", 368855]], "time_left_end": "270", "answered_time": 368855, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "270", "question_time_start": 368855, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 375199]], "time_left_end": "264", "answered_time": 375199, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "264", "question_time_start": 375199, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 378583]], "time_left_end": "260", "answered_time": 378583, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "260", "question_time_start": 378583, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 382680]], "time_left_end": "256", "answered_time": 382680, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "256", "question_time_start": 382680, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["calc_3", 384764], ["calc_+", 385505], ["calc_7", 386245], ["calc_9", 386998], ["calc_+", 387731], ["calc_8", 388332], ["calc_8", 388487], ["calc_=", 389239], ["submit", 394615]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "244", "answered_time": 394615, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "244", "question_time_start": 394615, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 404313]], "time_left_end": "235", "answered_time": 404313, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "235", "question_time_start": 404313, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 410781]], "time_left_end": "228", "answered_time": 410781, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "228", "question_time_start": 410781, "question": "8+6+19", "correct_answer": 33, "events": [["submit", 418584]], "time_left_end": "220", "answered_time": 418584, "user_answer": "33", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 418585, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "220", "question_time_start": 418585, "question": "4+6+9+33", "correct_answer": 52, "events": [["submit", 424473]], "time_left_end": "214", "answered_time": 424473, "user_answer": "52", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "214", "question_time_start": 424473, "question": "19+56", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 432200]], "time_left_end": "207", "answered_time": 432200, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "207", "question_time_start": 432200, "question": "96+854", "correct_answer": 950, "events": [["calc_8", 434679], ["calc_5", 435480], ["calc_4", 436137], ["calc_+", 436865], ["calc_9", 437780], ["calc_6", 438364], ["calc_=", 438948], ["submit", 444834]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "194", "answered_time": 444834, "user_answer": "950", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "194", "question_time_start": 444834, "question": "96+98", "correct_answer": 194, "events": [["submit", 449152]], "time_left_end": "190", "answered_time": 449152, "user_answer": "184", "user_correct": "False", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "190", "question_time_start": 449153, "question": "9+46+73", "correct_answer": 128, "events": [["submit", 465498]], "time_left_end": "173", "answered_time": 465498, "user_answer": "128", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "173", "question_time_start": 465499, "question": "8+6+84", "correct_answer": 98, "events": [["calc_8", 469662], ["calc_+", 470464], ["calc_6", 471046], ["calc_+", 471789], ["calc_8", 472430], ["calc_4", 472936], ["calc_=", 473680], ["submit", 478052]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "161", "answered_time": 478052, "user_answer": "98", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "161", "question_time_start": 478052, "question": "8+3+3+69", "correct_answer": 83, "events": [["submit", 486263]], "time_left_end": "153", "answered_time": 486263, "user_answer": "83", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "153", "question_time_start": 486263, "question": "9+29+78", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 503663]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 503663, "user_answer": "106", "user_correct": "False", "score": "14"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 503663, "question": "3+6+9+26", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["calc_6", 512945], ["calc_+", 513994], ["calc_3", 514636], ["calc_+", 515314], ["calc_9", 515996], ["calc_+", 516705], ["calc_2", 517633], ["calc_6", 518187], ["calc_=", 518930], ["submit", 523346]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "116", "answered_time": 523346, "user_answer": "44", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "116", "question_time_start": 523347, "question": "3+9+39", "correct_answer": 51, "events": [["submit", 526780]], "time_left_end": "112", "answered_time": 526780, "user_answer": "51", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 526780, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "112", "question_time_start": 526780, "question": "13+846", "correct_answer": 859, "events": [["submit", 536430]], "time_left_end": "102", "answered_time": 536430, "user_answer": "859", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "102", "question_time_start": 536430, "question": "19+14", "correct_answer": 33, "events": [["submit", 541396]], "time_left_end": "98", "answered_time": 541396, "user_answer": "33", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "98", "question_time_start": 541397, "question": "4+4+6+37", "correct_answer": 51, "events": [["submit", 547099]], "time_left_end": "92", "answered_time": 547099, "user_answer": "51", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "92", "question_time_start": 547099, "question": "7+9+4+38", "correct_answer": 58, "events": [["submit", 553262]], "time_left_end": "86", "answered_time": 553262, "user_answer": "58", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "86", "question_time_start": 553263, "question": "9+88+49", "correct_answer": 146, "events": [["calc_9", 555786], ["calc_+", 556496], ["calc_8", 557299], ["calc_8", 557452], ["calc_+", 558268], ["calc_4", 559070], ["calc_9", 559999], ["calc_=", 560833], ["submit", 566677]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "72", "answered_time": 566677, "user_answer": "146", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "72", "question_time_start": 566677, "question": "9+34+93", "correct_answer": 136, "events": [["calc_9", 569287], ["calc_+", 570135], ["calc_3", 571629], ["calc_4", 572349], ["calc_+", 573365], ["calc_9", 573917], ["calc_3", 574646], ["calc_=", 575879], ["submit", 580763]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "58", "answered_time": 580763, "user_answer": "136", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "58", "question_time_start": 580763, "question": "3+9+8+98", "correct_answer": 118, "events": [["submit", 590563]], "time_left_end": "48", "answered_time": 590563, "user_answer": "118", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "48", "question_time_start": 590563, "question": "7+4+24", "correct_answer": 35, "events": [["submit", 595295]], "time_left_end": "44", "answered_time": 595295, "user_answer": "35", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "44", "question_time_start": 595295, "question": "54+83", "correct_answer": 137, "events": [["submit", 604161]], "time_left_end": "35", "answered_time": 604161, "user_answer": "137", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "35", "question_time_start": 604162, "question": "8+9+29", "correct_answer": 46, "events": [["submit", 614280]], "time_left_end": "25", "answered_time": 614280, "user_answer": "46", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 614280, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "25", "question_time_start": 614280, "question": "57+294", "correct_answer": 351, "events": [["submit", 624412]], "time_left_end": "15", "answered_time": 624412, "user_answer": "351", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "15", "question_time_start": 624412, "question": "7+4+9+23", "correct_answer": 43, "events": [["submit", 628179]], "time_left_end": "11", "answered_time": 628178, "user_answer": "43", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "11", "question_time_start": 628179, "question": "4+73+99", "correct_answer": 176, "events": []}}}}}